Konstantin Polyashenko

Carmichael, California kman239@gmail.com • (916) 956-1830 • konopoly.github.io

SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated, detail driven student, who is passionate for technology. Through several internships I have professional experience implementing successful projects and solutions. I am a skilled problem solver who possesses a broad range of experience within the Software Development field.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science at California State University, Sacramento

Relevant Courses:

Introduction to Logic Design, Data Structures and Algorithm Analysis, Computer Organization, Computer Software Engineering, Object-Oriented Computer Graphics Programming, Programming Concepts and Methodology, Computer Networks and Internets, Operating System Principles*, Computer Theory and Programming Languages*, Database Management and File Organization*

*Spring 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, Sacramento, California, USA

Software Development Intern

Sep 2014 – Mar 2015

Developed a web application to predict and display weather and river patterns. Remodeled and updated outdated infrastructure and development tools. Migrated applications from Tcl/Tk to a modern python environment.

Covered California, Sacramento, California, USA

Student Intern

Jan 2014 - Jul 2014

Worked as part of the IT team. Responded to user requests for service, handled issue troubleshooting, and deployed solutions. Wrote scripts and applications to increase the productivity of the IT team.

SKILLS

Technical Skills: Java, Object Oriented Design, MySQL, Ruby, JavaScript **Core Competencies:** Software Testing, Analytical Skills, Problem Solving

PROJECTS

West Slope Recovery Center

Using the agile software development methodology implemented a software solution for a non profit start-up. Worked in a six person team to design, implement and deploy an application that allows employees to manage billing and scheduling. Data Visualization Tool

Developed a web application that allows users to easily graph and chart data files. Written in JavaScript and utilising the Highcharts API.

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS & ACTIVITIES

Association for Computing Machinery, California, USA

Active Member 2012 – Present

Math, Engineering and Science Achievements, California, USA

Active Member 2012 – Present

Competitive Robotics at CSUS, California, USA

Active Member 2012 – Present